I'll say it right up front, one of my favorites that we've had on the show before is Amanda Seals, comedian, actress, and now politician, or at least politician for the sake of her new comedy special, which is really, it's not even, it's kind of a political documentary.
Yeah, it's not a comedy special like you would think of Charles, right?
It's still plenty funny.
It is funny.
But I guess Amanda wanted to dip her toes into the political world.
I'm not sure why anybody would want to do that at this point, but if you can get some laughs out of it, then why not?
So the special is called, or the documentary is called, In Amanda We Trust, and Candidate Seals is joining us right now to talk about it.
Amanda, welcome back to TMZ Live.
Thank y'all so much.
Thank you so much.
You know, it's funny you're saying, why would anyone want to dip their toe in politics?
And that's the premise of the whole project is, you know, my following on Instagram.
They love to tell, well, my supporters, following sounds a little cultish, which actually sounds right up where politics is.
Right, exactly.
But they are adamant about, like, Amanda, you need to run for office.
You need to run for president.
You have common sense.
And I was like, you know what?
There was something there.
So we dabble with the idea, and we went around and asked some people that would know whether or not this is the space to go in throughout this project.
And I feel like in the midst, we teach, we laugh, we learn.
It's a good time.
So I get why your followers, I mean, sorry, your supporters would say that.
Look, you are certainly outspoken when it comes to political happenings in this country.
I'm one of your supporters, so I've seen the things that you have to say.
Thank you.
And so I get why your supporters would say that, that they want you to get into this.
But what I thought was interesting, I think I know you agree with this, that the state of politics right now in America is that it is very tribal.
It is, everyone is in their own silo, and it's an echo chamber where you're hearing your own side.
Yeah.
So what I saw, at least in the trailer, you do speak to some politicians, you speak to some members of Congress.
The ones that we see in the trailer were only Democrats.
I'm wondering if you spoke to any Republican politicians or Republican supporters that were in D.C.
Well, you know, I don't need to, because they say the same things everywhere and all the time.
So it's not like they're going to tell me anything new.
But the purpose of this project is really just to get people more excited about their involvement in civics and in government, right?
I feel like a lot of folks feel like it's this way out of touch, you know, that it's only reserved for certain people, that it's none of their business, that they don't need to be bothered.
And I'm like, yo, like this, there's a whole system in place that is determining how you live.
And if you're frustrated about things or you're annoyed about things, being a part of that system of understanding that system is going to be the first step to being able to change it.
So, Amanda, is the idea here that you're sort of encouraging people get involved?
You know, I mean, what comes to mind?
I am adamantly stating through this project that we have become a country where we have let our own ignorance be the thing that's hurting us.
And that is something that we are seeing politicians weaponize, right?
They are absolutely making the choice now to say, oh, let's keep people dumb.
Let's make them feel like we're the ones who they need to make the change.
And it's like, y'all, they used to be you.
These people used to be you.
Like, they were just regular Joe.
And they said, you know what, I want to have power.
But some said, I want to serve the people.
And that's what we need to get behind.
Amanda, would you want to hold office?
Obviously, you're so passionate.
You're up on the issues.
Would you want to hold office?
Ooh, child.
I am not someone who believes that I can create change from the inside.
Also, I love the people.
I do.
But I ain't trying to talk to the people every day.
I can't do it.
And, you know, then we found out that the people, a lot of them don't want to wash their hands.
So it's like, I can't even shake hands and kiss babies because I don't know where you've been.
I don't know where you've been.
That is a hazard of being a politician.
For me, I'm a comic.
I'm a creative.
And ultimately, this is where I'm supposed to be in order to be a part of changing the minds and hopefully changing the direction of where we're going into somewhere positive.
So you're not in office, but you're still doing your part.
And you're dressing.
I'm doing my part.
And I'm doing my part independently.
And you're dressing like you're in office.
I like that you stuck with the blazer.
Did you keep that from, you're like, hey, I like this.
This is from my closet.
Yeah, this is from my new legislative look closet.
I should get a line called the Seals Legislative, the Seals the Deal Legislative Look.
Yes, Seals the Deal.
I like it.
So people can check it out starting tomorrow.
It will be available through Patreon.
Yes, at InAmandaWeTrust.com.
So come through, support true artistry, support independent artists, and support work that's about supporting us.
Yes, ultimately.
This is, you can have a good laugh and you can also learn a lot too.
Amanda, thank you so much for putting this together in Amanda We Trust.
People should check that out.
And thanks for coming in and talk to us about it.
Seals the deal.
Thanks, Amanda.
All right, Amanda.
Thanks.